sup everyone television 5 you with a
very special video today now I just got
done watching true story
you're the Disney moving [ __ ] I've never
washed it until today because like my
parents as a kid they would let me watch
it cuz would they they told me that
buzzer were there like gay and [ __ ] like
I guess they have butt sex like that
they told me it was for adults only so I
wasn't out to watch it now I only was
like 50 minutes of the movie so I I
guess that counts as wasn't home movie
for me so let me talk about the two
things I liked about it one really wore
yellow like Bobby and he kind of had
blue pants too like they were jeans so I
guess you could say they're blue so like
you're like a walking about Bardonic
pictures if you ask me in Moroccan bars
also had a really big ass like I guess
like I don't know how dizzy let that
through but it was big as far I'd I'd
own them actually I don't man but how
big it was because I just I just was
like 15 minutes but in my mind it's the
well member of bothers ass was huge like
I'm not kidding and [ __ ] like it it was
like suck on ground like how all the
characters are gonna have big asses but
it wasn't as good a sock on the ground
if you're catching my drift
another thing I wanted to talk about was
they he his boys his armor was like
green and [ __ ] like Mac the Hedgehog and
he also had like this a weird purple
right extinct around his head which car
made him look like Queen Aleena rock
songs mama you know cuz she had she has
like purple hair and shared lock lock
buzzes latex thing with purple now let
me just say my mama wasn't kidding me
when she said that brother woody when I
gasps [ __ ]
like I was in 10-minute and it's in the
video when Buzz Lightyear came flying in
and
outside the wrapping the buzzer woody
we're gonna have sex raw on Andy's floor
but that didn't happen obviously like
maybe happens today in the film I don't
know I'd only watch 50 minutes so to end
off this review I'll just state the
obvious you don't you don't have to
watch the Toy Story if you're gonna
watch anything go watch Sonic
Underground if you want a show with
actual good [ __ ] like like you want good
music go to sock on down you want cool
fatties
go to sock on around you want to cool
that [ __ ] that's not buzzing way the
Bionic [ __ ] I mean that's all I gotta
say like why'd you [ __ ] Buzz Lightyear
with really when you can ship the best
ship of them all Dalby monk failed resin
x's [ __ ] sock the Hedgehog like it it
just don't make sense [ __ ] how how much
more clear do I gotta make this I mean
the love between Buzz and Woody pales in
comparison to the love of the lovers
[ __ ]
the reason Sonica Bobby's love all the
powers buzzing Woody's not ten falling
[ __ ] is is because you could tell sock
about like they love each other
unlike buzzer worthy the well they just
don't [ __ ] I mean if you like to see
I'm not bashing you and [ __ ]
I'm just saying you got you got [ __ ]
taste you could be watching sock on
around but you're not I mean I'm sorry
but your [ __ ] stupid [ __ ]